{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Greater than or equal to","correct_answer":">=","incorrect_answers":["> || =","> or =","<="]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What Javascript code matches this statement: Their name is Kim and they are less than 16 years old","correct_answer":"if (name === 'Kim' && age < 16 )","incorrect_answers":["if (name = 'Kim' && age < 16 )","if (name = 'Kim' || age < 16 )","if (name === 'Kim' || age < 16 )"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What symbol represents the and operator in JavaScript?","correct_answer":"&&","incorrect_answers":["and","&","AND"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What symbol represents the or operator in JavaScript?","correct_answer":"||","incorrect_answers":["or","OR","|"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Comparision Operators : What is == ? ","correct_answer":"Equal value and equal type","incorrect_answers":["Equal to ","Not equal","Not equal value or not equal type"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Comparision Operators : What is === ? ","correct_answer":"Not equal","incorrect_answers":["Equal value and equal type","Equal to","Not equal value or not equal type"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Comparison Operators : What is != ?","correct_answer":"Not equal value or not equal type","incorrect_answers":["Equal value and equal type","Not equal","Equal to"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Comparision Operators : What is ! == ?","correct_answer":"Equal to ","incorrect_answers":["Equal value and equal type","Not equal","Not equal value or not equal type"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Comparison Operators : What is >= ?","correct_answer":"Greater thanGreater than or equal to","incorrect_answers":["Less than","Greater than","Less than or equal to"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Comparison Operator : What is <= ?","correct_answer":"Less than or equal to ","incorrect_answers":["Less than","Greater than or equal to","Greater than"]}]}
